Piper Schwartz

(405) 888-2170 / piperschwartz@aol.com 801 S Cherry Street, Unit 421, Glendale, CO, 80246

Profile

My motivation and positivity shines through my work and daily life. I am a quick learner, and I believe my willingness to take on new challenges with creativity and enthusiasm helps me expand my knowledge even more. Although I spent years working in Hospitality, Web Development is my first true love. Having worked at many different restaurants, I got a change to work with a variety of technologies along the way.

Experience

SALES ASSOCIATE, BED BATH AND BEYOND, GLENDALE, DENVER JULY 2019- PRESENT

My duties include helping customers, stock control, online ordering, and cashiering. Supporting the supervisors wherever needed

SUPERVISOR/SERVER, TACOS TEQUILA WHISKEY, HIGHLANDS, DENVER APRIL 2019-JULY 2019

As a supervisor I am in charge of the bar, floor, and kitchen. Duties include the end of shift report, supporting the staff, banking, making sure all complaints and conflicts are addressed, and much more. As a server I take orders, run drinks, handle payments, and make sure the guest experience is top notch.

INTERN/SERVER, CHARLESTON'S RESTAURANT, OKLAHOMA CITY, OK- MAY 2013- AUGUST 2015 / SEPTEMBER 2018-FEBRUARY 2019

As an intern, I was able to carry out duties in all aspects of the restaurant. I was able to learn and develop management skills. I continued as a head waiter after the internship ended, doing the administrative side of managing at the end of the shift as well as working as wait staff.

WAIT STAFF/ CAFE ALL-ROUNDER, PRIMAL PANTRY YAGAN SQUARE, WESTERN AUS - MAY 2018-AUGUST 2018

Being a barista, making wraps, salads and other products, handling cash, etc

TEAM LEADER/SUPERVISOR, HOLIDAY INN PERTH CITY CENTRE- IVY AND JACK, WESTERN AUSTRALIA- JULY 2017-APRIL 2018

Helping the staff to the best of my ability and being on the floor with them so I can be hands-on. Guest conflict resolution and service recovery is a requirement. My duties were also the banking at the end of the shift, and the reports. I was in charge of the floor staff, bar staff, as well as the room service staff. Being cross trained at this venue is a must, therefore I have a wide range of skills and abilities.

WAIT STAFF/ SUPERVISOR, THE PRECINCT RESTAURANT, WESTERN AUSTRALIA- APRIL 2016 UNTIL APRIL 2017

Ensured accuracy of orders and cash handling. Implemented customer service techniques to ensure exceptional service for guests. Managed, trained, and advised new staff. Practiced general bartending.

WAIT STAFF, LUCKY CHAN'S NOODLE AND LAUNDRY BAR, WESTERN AUSTRALIA- FEBRUARY 2016 UNTIL MAY 2016

Making sure the shifts ran smoothly by demonstrating my best customer service by ensuring guests received the correct food, drinks and have a memorable experience.

WAIT STAFF, TUCK SHOP CAFE, WESTERN AUSTRALIA- OCTOBER 2015 UNTIL APRIL 2016

Meeting the needs of the guests, giving fast and accurate service.

RAMBLA ON SWAN, WESTERN AUSTRALIA - DECEMBER 2015 UNTIL JANUARY 2016

All around staff member. Helped in the dining room, worked the pass, ran food and drinks. I worked the New Year's Eve event, which meant supervising a large section and verifying that the guests got the experience they paid for.

VILLA ATTENDANT, BYRON NELSON GOLF TOURNAMENT AT THE FOUR SEASONS LOS COLINAS, LOS COLINAS, TEXAS-MAY 2015

In charge of 3 Company Villas in the Four Seasons during the Byron Nelson Golf Tournament, which is the largest banquet event in North America.

Manage all the guests attending the villas. Taking inventory at the end of each day. These guests pay about \$40,000 for a villa for the weekend, so it is up to the villa attendants to ensure they have exemplary customer service.

Skills

Excellent with technology. I have my Web Masters certificate. I am naturally tech savvy.

Passionate about helping others and a patient teacher/learner.

Thrive in fast-paced environments and thinking on my feet.

I pride myself on being able to keep a calm and level head under stress.

Working effectively and accurately.

Being organized and well-planned.

Education

Oklahoma State University- Stillwater 2011-2015

Bachelor of Science in Human Sciences with a Major of Hotel and Restaurant Administration

In this degree, we studied a range of aspects such as; Accounting, Cost Control, Human Resources, Management techniques, Quantity Food Preparation, Service, Food Safety and Sanitation, etc.

Murdoch University-Perth, WA Fall 2014

Study Abroad

Moore Norman Technology Centre 2009-2010

Web Design

University of Denver 2019

Full Stack Web Development Coding Bootcamp

References on request